{
    "subject": "resource/Adolph_Menzel",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathYear",
    "object": "1905",
    "human_readable": "Adolph Menzel died in 1905.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8724050521850586,
            "question": "In what year did Adolph Menzel die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4748380184173584,
            "question": "What was Adolph Menzel known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3731078505516052,
            "question": "Do you have any information about Adolph Menzel's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36621880531311035,
            "question": "Who were some contemporaries of Adolph Menzel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32532283663749695,
            "question": "Was Adolph Menzel a famous artist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28980928659439087,
            "question": "What artistic movements was Adolph Menzel associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26549607515335083,
            "question": "Is there any information about Adolph Menzel's influences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26469141244888306,
            "question": "Can you tell me about any notable works by Adolph Menzel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2525896430015564,
            "question": "Where did Adolph Menzel live and work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1256321370601654,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of Adolph Menzel's art style?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Adolph Menzel died in 1905.",
            "html": "dbpedia_664_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Adolph Menzel live and work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_664_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about any notable works by Adolph Menzel?",
            "html": "dbpedia_664_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about Adolph Menzel's influences?",
            "html": "dbpedia_664_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_664_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_664_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_664_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_664_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_664_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_664_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_664_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_664_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_664_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_664_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents confirm that Adolph Menzel lived from 1815 to 1905 and specifically mention that he died in 1905 at the age of 90. This supports the statement that he indeed died in 1905."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Adolph Menzel died in 1905, which matches the statement in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}